<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<document>
	<en>
		<header>Interpret control-panel light patterns</header>
		<view_labels>»View control-panel labels</view_labels>
		<state_of_the_product>State of the product</state_of_the_product>
		<action>Action</action>
		<wlan_button>Wireless network button</wlan_button>
		<wlan_light>Wireless network light</wlan_light>
		<ready_light>Ready light</ready_light>
		<attn_light>Attention light</attn_light>
		<cancel_button>Cancel button</cancel_button>
		<allOff_title>All lights are off.</allOff_title>
		<allOff_stateBody>The product is in Auto-Off mode or is turned off.</allOff_stateBody>
		<allOff_actionBody>Press the power button to deactivate the Auto-Off mode or to turn on the product.</allOff_actionBody>
		<readyOn_title>Ready light is on, and attention light is off.</readyOn_title>
		<readyOn_stateBody>The product is in the ready state.</readyOn_stateBody>
		<readyOn_actionBody>No action is required. The product is ready to receive a print job.</readyOn_actionBody>
		<readyBlinking_title>Ready light is blinking, and attention light is off.</readyBlinking_title>
		<readyBlinking_stateBody>The product is receiving or processing data.</readyBlinking_stateBody>
		<readyBlinking_actionBody>No action is required. The product is receiving or processing a print job.</readyBlinking_actionBody>
		<attnBlinking_title>Attention light is blinking, and the ready light is off.</attnBlinking_title>
		<attnBlinking_stateBody>The product has experienced an error that can be corrected at the product, such as a jam, an open door, the absence of a print cartridge, or the absence of paper in the proper tray.</attnBlinking_stateBody>
		<attnBlinking_actionBody>Inspect the product, determine the error, and then correct the error. If the error is the absence of paper in the proper tray or the product is in a manual feed mode, put the proper paper in the tray and follow the onscreen instructions, or open and close the print-cartridge door to resume printing.</attnBlinking_actionBody>
		<alternating_title>Status lights cycle.</alternating_title>
		<alternating_stateBody>The status lights cycle when the product is processing a cleaning page.</alternating_stateBody>
		<alternating_actionBody>No action is required. The product should enter the ready state when the cleaning page is processed.</alternating_actionBody>
		<unison_title>Status lights blink in unison.</unison_title>
		<unison_stateBody>The status lights blink in unison during the formatter initialization period.</unison_stateBody>
		<unison_actionBody>No action is required. Wait for the initialization period to end. The product should enter the ready state when the initialization period is finished.</unison_actionBody>
		<readyOn_attnBlinking_title>Attention light is blinking, and ready light is on.</readyOn_attnBlinking_title>
		<readyOn_attnBlinking_stateBody>The product has experienced a continual error from which it will recover on its own.</readyOn_attnBlinking_stateBody>
		<readyOn_attnBlinking_actionBody>If the recovery is successful, the product continues to the Processing Data state and completes the job.

If the recovery is unsuccessful, the product continues to the Continuable Error state. Try removing any media from the media path and turning the product off, and then on again.</readyOn_attnBlinking_actionBody>
		<allOn_title>The attention and ready lights are on.</allOn_title>
		<allOn_stateBody>The product has experienced a fatal error from which it cannot recover.</allOn_stateBody>
		<allOn_actionBody>1. Turn off the product.
2. Wait 30 seconds, and then turn on the product or reconnect the power cord to the product.
3. Wait for the product to initialize. 

If the error persists, contact HP customer support.</allOn_actionBody>
		<wirelessBlinking_title>The wireless light is blinking.</wirelessBlinking_title>
		<wirelessBlinking_stateBody>The product is attempting to locate a wireless network.</wirelessBlinking_stateBody>
		<wirelessBlinking_actionBody>No action is required.</wirelessBlinking_actionBody>
		<wirelessOn_title>The wireless light is on.</wirelessOn_title>
		<wirelessOn_stateBody>The product is connected to a wireless network.</wirelessOn_stateBody>
		<wirelessOn_actionBody>No action is required.</wirelessOn_actionBody>
	</en>
</document>